​Who the hell are you?
你到底是谁
Park ranger.
公园巡逻员
Just put it down and I won't have to kill you.
放下枪   我不会杀你
This isn't a stand off. I've got the gun.
我有手枪   你身处下风
I never keep it loaded.
我从不上子弹
I thought you said it wasn't loaded.
你说枪内没子弹
I lied. Now, who the hell are you?
我撒谎   你究竟是谁
I'm a captain in the United States Air Force.
我是美国空军上尉
Well, Captain, you're under arrest.
上尉   你被捕了
If You told us, we can get thought it out.
事情弄明白后才放你
Lady, you're missing the bigger picture here.
女士   你根本不明白
Hold still.
别动
All right? I have already had a hell of a morning, lady.
明白吗   今早我已经够麻烦了   女士
Now, I can't tell you what's going on, but I need your help. OK?
不能告诉你发生什么事   但要你帮忙
This is a good way to convince me.
这种理由就能说服我吗
When both know the gun is loaded, so if I wanted, I could blow your head off. Right?
我们都知道枪里有子弹   我大可用这枪轰毙你
Yeah.
是
But I'm not going to.
但我不会
Come on.
来拿吧